compassweb.com 1999-04-24

# CompassWeb: About Compass: Privacy Policy

| 

Welcome to CompassWeb, Compass Bank’s corporate web site. This section explains Compass’ policy about personal information you supply when you visit this site. Our goal is to protect your information on CompassWeb in the same way we protect it when you use our banking centers, ATMs, or contact Compass by phone. 

**Compass Bank’s Internet Privacy Policy**

  1. **You don't have to provide information.**   
You can visit this site to find out about products and services, read corporate reports, check on career opportunities, or get stock quotes and other valuable services without providing any information about yourself.
  2.  **Any information you provide is confidential.**  
If you do provide personal information, such as an address, e-mail, telephone and fax numbers, customer identification or transaction information, we will not disclose (share, sell or divulge) it to any unaffiliated third parties without your consent. We will maintain this information, as well as your business activities and transactions, according to our usual security and confidentiality standards applicable to all customer information.
  3.  **Information is only shared with your consent or legal requirement.**  
We do not reveal specific information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data to unaffiliated third parties for their independent use, except for the exchange of information with reputable information reporting agencies to maximize the accuracy and security of such information or in the performance of bona fide corporate due diligence, unless 1) the information is provided to help complete a customer initiated transaction; 2) the customer requests it; 3) the disclosure is required by/or allowed by law (e.g., subpoena, investigation of fraudulent activity, etc.); or 4) the customer has been informed about the possibility of disclosure for marketing or similar purposes through a prior communication and is given the opportunity to decline (i.e., “opt out”).
  4.  **CompassWeb may use a software “cookie”.**  
In order to provide better service, we may use a “cookie”. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes; for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information. No cookie will contain any information that would enable anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or U.S. mail. 

(A cookie is a small piece of information which a web site stores in the web browser of your PC and can later retrieve. A cookie cannot be read by a web site other than the one that set the cookie. Most cookies only last through a single session or visit. You can set up your web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set.) 

| 
|  | This section explains Compass’ policy about personal information you supply when you visit this site. Our goal is to protect your information on CompassWeb in the same way we protect it when you use our banking centers, ATMs, or contact Compass by phone. Our policy is as follows: ****

  1. **You don't have to provide information.** You can visit this site to find out about products and services, read corporate reports, check on career opportunities, or get stock quotes and other valuable services without providing any information about yourself.
  2.  **Any information you provide is confidential.** If you do provide personal information, such as an address, e-mail, telephone and fax numbers, customer identification or transaction information, we will not disclose (share, sell or divulge) it to any unaffiliated third parties without your consent. We will maintain this information, as well as your business activities and transactions, according to our usual security and confidentiality standards applicable to all customer information.
  3.  **Information is only shared with your consent or legal requirement.** We do not reveal specific information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data to unaffiliated third parties for their independent use, except for the exchange of information with reputable information reporting agencies to maximize the accuracy and security of such information or in the performance of bona fide corporate due diligence, unless 1) the information is provided to help complete a customer initiated transaction; 2) the customer requests it; 3) the disclosure is required by/or allowed by law (e.g., subpoena, investigation of fraudulent activity, etc.); or 4) the customer has been informed about the possibility of disclosure for marketing or similar purposes through a prior communication and is given the opportunity to decline (i.e., “opt out”).
  4.  **CompassWeb may use a software “cookie”.** In order to provide better service, we may use a “cookie”. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes; for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information. No cookie will contain any information that would enable anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or U.S. mail. 

(A cookie is a small piece of information which a web site stores in the web browser of your PC and can later retrieve. A cookie cannot be read by a web site other than the one that set the cookie. Most cookies only last through a single session or visit. You can set up your web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set.) 

|  | Return to CompassWeb home
